http://www.elkislandretreat.com/privacy-policy

Experiences/
Camper Information/AmenitiesRatesWeddings/Reunions/EventsRegulationsReservation Cancellation Policy
Contact/
EIR Events/
... a great place to unwind.
Experiences/
Camper Information/AmenitiesRatesWeddings/Reunions/EventsRegulationsReservation Cancellation Policy
Contact/
EIR Events/
Privacy Policy
Elk Island Retreat collects information anonymously from users who visit our web site. This information is also collected for statistical analysis. While on the site Elk Island Retreat collects the following non-personal information such as: your IP address, your domain, your browser information, operating system information, referral data, service provider and local time. Any personal information that you voluntarily provide to us, such as booking information, will be collected and used by us on an internal basis only. We will never share any personal information which was collected with your consent.By attending our events you are giving your consent to be photographed. These photos may be used for promotional and advertising purposes. Guardians of minors also accept these terms for use in promotional/advertising both in print and online.Your credit card will be charged for any missing items or damages that occur at your site during your stay. Elk Island Retreat Ltd. owners, staff or volunteers cannot be held responsible or liable for injuries, loss or damages incurred by guests or otherwise during your stay.It is each campers responsibility to read, understand and follow the Campground Rules.
Follow us on Instagram
View fullsize
View fullsize
View fullsize
View fullsize
View fullsize
View fullsize
View fullsize
Terms of Use l Privacy Policy l Reservation / Cancellation Policy
